getyourbillspaid.co.uk 2007-12-15

# 

L2 Multimedia, LLC. (“Company”) respects your right to privacy. Your continued use of our website and your submission of any information to us indicate that you have read, understand and agree to our Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy will tell you:   
• What information the Company collects.   
• How the Company may share information.   
• How you can let us know your preference for sharing of information. 

**Please note that your information will be collected, processed and stored on servers located in the United States. Although the laws regarding data protection in the United States may be less stringent than those in the United Kingdom, the Company will collect, process and store your information in a confidential and secure environment. By registering on this website, you acknowledge that the Company operates in the United States and you agree to permit the Company to transmit and use your personal information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this website. 

If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with any information or use any of the products or services offered or provided on Company websites. 

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE PROTECT IT? 

Consumer Information   
We receive information about you when you register on one of our websites or on one of our affiliate’s or partner’s websites, or when you take part in a special promotion or fill out a form on one of our websites or on one of our affiliate’s, partner’s or advertiser’s websites. The information we collect may include: 

• Your e-mail addres   
• Your name   
• Your postal address   
• Your telephone number   
• Your date of birth   
• Your gender   
• Your title   
• Your marital status

This information may also include any other personal information or unique preference information you choose to provide. 

Information from Other Sources   
We may receive information about you from other sources. This information may help us to improve our ability to service your needs on a personalized basis. It helps us to learn more about you and your shopping preferences and also helps us let you know about new offers we think you might like. 

Automatic Information   
We want you to be aware that certain tools exist to help us service and recognize you. For your convenience, to help us personalize your experience or better serve your needs, we may receive and store certain types of information when you visit one of our websites. You may be familiar with the term “cookies,” which are unique alphanumeric identifiers that store your personal information. These cookies are placed on your computer when your web browser accesses our websites. We use this information for tracking purposes, to deliver content specific to your interests and to educate us on things such as how you navigate to and around our websites, product browsing, content accessing, and purchasing data. If you choose, there are utilities available for purchase from independent software providers to install on your computer as well as tools/preferences you can choose through most web browsers to make website visits anonymous. Of course, cookies let you have a more satisfying website experience, so we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

Information Required by the Government   
The Company may be required to collect and submit certain information required by the government. This information, which may include your taxpayer identification number, will not be used, shared, transferred, or sold for marketing purposes. 

ONCE INFORMATION IS RECEIVED, HOW IS IT USED AND SHARED?   
We may use the collected information for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to customer service, to provide you with products, services or information you have requested, to customize your user experience, for internal business purposes, and for marketing purposes, including our online and offline programs and services. 

Within the Company   
We share information we collect from all points of contact within the Company network, including with our parent company and with any other subsidiaries or divisions of our parent company. The information you give us and information about your transaction may be combined with other personally identifiable information available from our records and other sources. 

Carefully Selected Companies and Organizations   
We may share your information with various vendors, business partners, technology providers, service providers, and other organizations which are not part of the Company. These companies and organizations may use the information we provide to them to serve advertisements or assist us in serving your needs. These disclosures also may be made to help us enforce or apply existing terms and conditions and/or other agreements or to protect the rights, property or safety of our websites, our users or others. When you indicate your interest in receiving information, products or services from a third party advertiser on a Company website, your personal information will be provided to that advertiser. Further, we may share your information with third party advertisers and marketers for various marketing purposes, including their on-line and/or off-line programs or services. Finally, we may share your information with carefully selected partners for data validation, enhancement, information verification and suppression services, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference or look-up services. 

Governmental Agencies or Other Companies   
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when (1) permitted or required by law, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. In all cases, this information is not provided to these entities for marketing purposes. 

Right to Transfer   
Should the Company choose to sell or transfer business assets, it is possible that the information we possess may be transferred as part of that transaction. The Company may decide to retain a copy of the information post sale or transfer. 

DATA PROCESSING/SAFE HARBOR   
The European Union (“EU”) maintains strict privacy laws. These rules differ significantly from United States laws. To reconcile these differences, the United States and the EU have created a Safe Harbor that defines mutually acceptable privacy operations. The Company adheres to the Safe Harbor principals. For more information please go to [_www.export.gov/safeharbor_](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor). 

By providing information to the Company, you acknowledge that it operates in the United States and agree (i) to permit the Company to transmit and use your personal information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this website, and (ii) that such use by the Company shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy and applicable Terms and Conditions. 

COMPANY CUSTOMER CHOICES   
E-mail   
By completing and submitting one of our forms or our partner’s forms, you are consenting to receive commercial e-mail from the Company and third parties that informs you about new merchandise, sales, special discounts and promotions. In addition, we may send you e-mail to help us learn more about you and your preferences. If, after you have shared your e-mail address with the Company, you decide that you do not want to receive e-mail from the Company, you can discontinue promotional e-mail by clicking on the hyperlink shown in all Company e-mails and follow the directions to indicate your unsubscribe preference. If you have registered or submitted information under more than one e-mail account, you must submit separate unsubscribe requests from each account. 

Note that you may continue to receive e-mail from entities other than the Company. 

Request for More Information/Updating your Information   
As it relates to e-mail communications or any other questions you might have about our Privacy Policy, or to update your information, or inquire as to what information is held about you, please contact us by e-mail at [_privacy@getyourbillspaid.co.uk_](mailto:privacy@getyourbillspaid.co.uk) or write to us at L2Multimedia, LLC 1158 26th Street, Suite 707 Santa Monica, CA 90403

**WHAT HAPPENS IF I HIT A LINK TO ANOTHER SITE FROM A COMPANY SITE?**   
Our websites may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you should review the policies that govern that particular site. 

APPLICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY   
This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to the Company. Other affiliated entities of the Company may obtain information independently from transactions and experiences with you or from other sources. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to that information. 

WHAT IS THE POLICY WITH RESPECT TO COMMUNICATING WITH CHILDREN?   
We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information through any point of contact, we ask to be contacted at [_privacy@getyourbillspaid.co.uk_](mailto:privacy@getyourbillspaid.co.uk) and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files. 

SECURITY   
Our Commitment to Data Security   
There is no such thing as complete security on the Internet or otherwise. The Company uses industry standard security techniques on our websites to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information we’ve collected from you. When you access your personal information or transmit personally identifiable data to us, that information is stored on servers that we have protected from unauthorized access or intrusion. While we strive to protect your information, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with the Company, its partners and affiliates. 

YOUR CONSENT   
By submitting information to us, you consent to the Company’s use of the information collected or submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. We may change or add to this Privacy Policy so we encourage you to review it periodically. In order to track any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will include a historical reference at the end of this Privacy Policy. This will begin at the next subsequent revision following the posting of this dated edition.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY   
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE. YOU AGREE THAT THE COMPANY’S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY THE COMPANY TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.    

Date of Last Modification: June 14, 2007

Copyright 2007, L2 Multimedia, LLC All Rights Reserved
